http://www.teensource.org/terms-of-use

Skip to main content
Show Mobile Menu
Find a ClinicBirth ControlLong Term Birth Control MethodsBarrier MethodsHormonal Birth Control MethodsOther MethodsSTDsChlamydiaHuman Papillomavirus (HPV)GonorrheaHIV (AIDS)Hepatitis BHerpesSyphilisTrichomoniasisRelationshipsHealthy RelationshipsSexuality + Gender IdentityFamilyPeersBlogsKnow Your RightsConfidentialityAffordabilityCare During School HoursEmergency ContraceptionPregnant + Parenting TeensAccessing Services as a MinorComprehensive Sex EdVote!Consent: Yes Means Yes
Social Links
Home
»
Terms of Use
Terms of Use
Article Media
PLEASE READ THESE TERMS OF USE CAREFULLY BECAUSE THEY DESCRIBE YOUR RIGHTS AND RESPONSIBILITIES.TERMS OF USE
The Terms of Use are effective as of Feb 5. 2007.TeenSource.org is an educational website as an online resource for sexuality and health-related information for visitors thirteen years of age and older. If you are not yet thirteen years old, you must exit this site now.By visiting this site, you agree to comply with the Terms of Use and you accept our Privacy Policy, found here. Please read the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy now and check regularly for future changes. If you use the TeenSource.org website, we will assume that you have read the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy and you agree to and accept both. If for any reason you do not agree with the terms and conditions described in the Terms of Use and our Privacy Policy, please exit this site immediately, because by using or attempting to use the TeenSource.org website, you are agreeing to be legally bound by both.INTRODUCTIONTeenSource.org is committed to providing honest, easy to understand information about sexual health, relationships, and issues affecting teens and young adults today. To that end, the resources on the TeenSource.org website are provided for your personal education and entertainment. Please understand, however, that this website is not a substitute for in-person medical care. Nothing on this site constitutes a diagnosis or recommendation for any specific medical treatment, nor does TeenSource.org make a warranty of any kind about the appropriateness of these resources for individual on-line visitors. It’s your job to be smart about your health and your life. Educate yourself with reliable information about sexual and reproductive health, and be sure to visit a qualified health care professional or clinic whenever necessary for personal medical evaluation, counseling, and services.1. INFORMATION PROVIDED ON THE TEENSOURCE.ORG WEBSITE DOES NOT CONSTITUTE MEDICAL, LEGAL, OR OTHER PROFESSIONAL ADVICEThe information contained in or discussed on the TeenSource.org website, or transmitted to you electronically, telephonically, or by U.S. Mail in response to a request or submission from you, is not intended nor implied to qualify as medical advice, diagnosis of a medical condition, or treatment for any medical condition, nor should this information be construed as psychological counseling or any emotional or mental health diagnosis or treatment. All information is based on current health information and education resources. We are not medical professionals, and this website does not directly or indirectly practice medicine or dispense medical advice as part of this service. We urge you to always seek professional health services for any concerns you may have about your personal physical, emotional, or mental health.In addition, nothing contained in this website is intended to be or constitutes legal advice, and you should always seek the advice of a qualified attorney or other appropriate professional if you have questions or concerns of a legal or professional nature.2. MODIFICATIONSWe reserve the right, at any time, for any reason at our sole discretion, to change the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy. We will post or display notices of change on this website, along with the effective date of such changes. If you use the website after the date the changes become effective, your use will signify your agreement to be bound by the changes. You should check back frequently and review the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy regularly so you are aware of the most current rights and obligations that apply to you.3. OWNERSHIP OF INTELLECTUAL PROPERTYThe entire TeenSource.org website, including, without limitation, the software, design, text, images, illustrations, graphics, photographs, artwork, sound, music, videos (such as music videos, scenes, movie clips, testimonials, and video clinic tours), scripts, interactive features, and other original materials within this website, and their selection and arrangement, (“Content”), and the trademarks, service marks, and logos contained therein (“Marks”), are owned by or licensed to TeenSource.org, and are subject to copyright and other intellectual property rights and protections under United States federal and state law, foreign laws, and international conventions. TeenSource.org reserves all rights in and to the Content and the Marks, unless expressly granted.It is absolutely prohibited to download, reprint, or electronically reproduce all or any part of the Content in quantity or for commercial use, and you shall not download, reproduce, modify, create derivative works from, display, perform, publish, distribute, disseminate, broadcast or circulate to any third party (including, without limitation, on or via a third party website), or otherwise use, all or any part of the Content without the express prior written consent of TeenSource.org.If you would like to download or print out a copy of the Content for your personal, non-commercial use, you may do so, but only if you keep all copyright and other proprietary notices intact. For special copyright permissions, or to purchase videos, publications, pamphlets, or other materials, please write to:TeenSource.org 3600 Wilshire Boulevard, Suite 600 Los Angeles, California 90010Or send an email to: teensourceorg@gmail.comTeenSource, TeenSource.org, and Are You Gettin' It? are the federally registered trademarks.The unauthorized or prohibited use of any of the above registered trademarks or copyrighted materials may subject you to civil liability or criminal prosecution, or both, under applicable U.S. federal and state laws, as well as foreign laws and international conventions.4. DISCLAIMER OF WARRANTY AND LIMITATION ON LIABILITYTeenSource.org assumes no liability for any diagnosis, treatment, decision you make, or action you take, or fail to take, in reliance upon information contained in the TeenSource.org website or any Internet sites linked to it in any way. TeenSource.org assumes no responsibility or risk for your use of the TeenSource.org website, any website connected to the TeenSource.org website by hyperlink, any other website, or the Internet, nor does TeenSource.org assume any liability for your selection or use of any clinic or health care provider shown or described on this website.In addition, TeenSource.org makes no express or implied warranties, representations, or endorsements whatsoever in connection with the TeenSource.org website, (including but not limited to any clinic or health care provider shown or described on the TeenSource.org website), other websites connected to the TeenSource.org website by hyperlink, or the Internet generally, (including, without limitation, warranties of title or non-infringement, or the implied warranties of merchantability or fitness for a particular purpose). Except for information, products, or services clearly identified as being supplied by TeenSource.org. TeenSource.org does not review, operate, or control in any way any materials, information, products or services on the Internet, including those connected to the TeenSource.org website through hyperlinks, or those supplied by some other source.In no event shall TeenSource.org be liable for any injury, loss, claim, damage, or any incidental or consequential damages arising either directly or indirectly out of or in any way connected with the TeenSource.org website, or any failure or delay in updating or including any materials on the TeenSource.org website, or any use of or inability to use any materials on the TeenSource.org website, even if TeenSource.org has been advised of the possibility of such damages. (Some states do not allow the exclusion of implied warranties or the limitation or exclusion of liability for incidental and consequential damages, so the above exclusions may not apply to you.)5. YOUR PRIVACY ON THIS SITEYour use of the TeenSource.org website is also governed by our Privacy Policy, found here, which is incorporated herein by reference. If you use or attempt to use this website, you are consenting to the Terms of Use and our Privacy Policy, and you are agreeing to be bound by their provisions.6. WAIVER OF RESPONSIBILITY FOR DEFECTIVE OR CONTAMINATED MATERIALSWhile TeenSource.org works hard to see that no inaccurate or misleading data, opinions, or statements appear on the website, it is impossible to guarantee accuracy at all times. Therefore, all information on the TeenSource.org website is offered for general informational, educational, and entertainment purposes only, and TeenSource.org disclaims responsibility for any errors or omissions, such as unintended technical inaccuracies or typographical errors, in the materials.Furthermore, TeenSource.org cannot and does not guarantee or warrant that files available for downloading through this website will be free of infection or viruses, worms, Trojan Horses, or other code that contain contaminating or destructive properties. It is your responsibility to implement sufficient safeguards, procedures, and checkpoints to satisfy your particular requirements for accuracy of data input and output, and for maintaining a procedure outside the TeenSource.org website for the reconstruction of any lost data. Use of the TeenSource.org website and the Internet is at the visitor’s own risk.7. LEGAL ACTIONSThe Terms of Use and Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the substantive laws of the State of California, without regard to conflict of law provisions. In the event there is any dispute, claim, or cause of action arising out of or related to the TeenSource.org website, or the use of this website, you agree to exclusive personal jurisdiction and venue in the state and federal courts located in Los Angeles, California, and you agree that regardless of any statute or law to the contrary, any such dispute, claim, or cause of action must be filed within six months after it accrues.Either TeenSource.org or you may demand that any such dispute, claim, or cause of action be settled by arbitration in Los Angeles, California, provided that the foregoing shall not prevent TeenSource.org from seeking injunctive relief in a court of competent jurisdiction.8. CONTESTS AND PROMOTIONSFrom time to time, TeenSource.org may conduct contests or promotions on or in connection with the TeenSource.org website. Each such contest or promotion will have additional terms, conditions and rules (“Rules”) which will be posted or otherwise made available to you and, for purposes of each contest or promotion, the Rules will be deemed incorporated into and form a part of the Terms of Use. If any conflict arises between the Terms of Use and the Rules, the Rules shall govern for purposes of your participation or involvement in the promotion or contest to which the Rules relate.9. OTHER RULES(A) You may not submit or transmit any message that is obscene, libelous or defamatory, or that violates any other person's copyrights, privacy or publicity rights, trademarks, trade secrets, or rights in other confidential information. You agree to indemnify TeenSource.org for any and all damages suffered by third parties as a result of your violation of this paragraph.(B) You may not submit or transmit any message, data, image, or program with the intent to threaten the safety of others, or to cause others to believe that they are being threatened. TeenSource.org reserves the right to take such action as it deems appropriate in cases where the TeenSource.org website is inappropriately used to disseminate statements or materials that are reasonably construed as abusive, destructive, harmful, or threatening to the safety of others.(C) You may not interfere with other users' use of the TeenSource.org website, including, without limitation, disrupting the normal flow or use of the service.(D) You may not post or transmit any file which contains viruses, worms, Trojan Horses, or any other contaminating or destructive features.(E) The Terms of Use and Privacy Policy are accepted upon your use of the TeenSource.org website, and are further affirmed if and when you register at the website.10. GENERALThe Terms of Use, together with the Privacy Policy and any other legal notices published on the TeenSource.org website, shall constitute the entire agreement between you and TeenSource.org concerning your use of the TeenSource.org website and its services. If any portion of this Terms of Use is deemed by any court to be invalid, the remaining provisions shall remain in full force and effect. No waiver of any term of this Terms of Use shall be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or any other term, and TeenSource.org's failure to assert any right or provision under this Terms of Use shall not constitute a waiver of such right or provision.11. CONTACTING THE WEBSITEIf you have any questions about the Terms of Use or Privacy Policy, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, you can contact:TEENSOURCE.ORG 3600 WILSHIRE BOULEVARD, SUITE 600 LOS ANGELES, CALIFORNIA 90010 teensourceorg@gmail.com©2007, TeenSource.org. All rights reserved.TeenSource, TeenSource.org, and Are You Gettin' It? are the federally registered trademarks.
TeenSource Tip of the Week
Holiday romance movies may be fun but are not always the best example of a healthy relationship.
Text "TEENSOURCE" to 877877 to Signup
Get weekly sex info and life advice sent to you every week! You can also find the nearest clinic to you for low to no cost sexual health services. Message and data rates may apply. Text STOP to opt out. Terms and Conditions Privacy Policy Click here to learn more.
© Copyright 2015-2020. All Rights Reserved.
The images used on this website are for illustrative purposes only.
Any person depicted in these images is a model.
Human Papillomavirus (HPV)
Gonorrhea
Hepatitis B
Herpes
HIV (Aids)
